couponaholic.net 2019-10-13

# Privacy Policy

## Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We do run advertising banners and/or browser executable code that can allow our advertisers to track visitors to our site with cookies. We cannot control this behavior and the privacy policies of these vendors affect the use of these technology.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**_OUR TOP PICKS (UPDATED 10/7/19):_**

 **  
-[$18 FREE! ***NO Receipts Req’d*** Nature’s Way Class Action Lawsuit Settlement!](https://www.couponaholic.net/2019/10/18-free-no-receipts-reqd-natures-way-class-action-lawsuit-settlement/)   
-[Amazon: Almost 50% OFF Glad Trash Bags with stackable sales and discounts!](https://www.couponaholic.net/2019/10/amazon-almost-50-off-glad-trash-bags-with-stackable-sales-and-discounts/)   
-[HOT! ONLY $5.95 (plus FREE shipping) Baby Einstein Bundle with FOUR BOOKS!](https://www.couponaholic.net/2019/10/hot-only-5-95-plus-free-shipping-baby-einstein-bundle-with-four-books/)   
-[HOT! FREE + $1.52 PROFIT Rubbermaid TakeAlongs at Walmart (NEW Topcashback Members!)](https://www.couponaholic.net/2019/10/new-topcashback-members-2/)   
-[Amazon: ONLY $20.99 Highly-Rated 6-Cube Storage Rack Staircase Organizer w/sale!](https://www.couponaholic.net/2019/10/amazon-only-20-99-highly-rated-6-cube-storage-rack-staircase-organizer-w-sale/)   
-[Amazon: 51% OFF Gillette Men’s Disposable Razors w/coupon = $2.97!](https://www.couponaholic.net/2019/10/amazon-51-off-gillette-mens-disposable-razors-w-coupon-2-97/)   
-[EARN UP TO $25/HOUR with Shipt (AWESOME Side Gig for Extra Cash!)](https://www.couponaholic.net/2019/05/earn-up-to-25-hour-with-shipt-awesome-side-gig-for-extra-cash-2/)**

 ** _GET CONNECTED WITH COUPONAHOLIC:_**

 **
